ameya360.com 2018-11-15

# Privacy Policy | Ameya360Electronics

## Privacy Policy

Ameye360 respects your right to privacy. We developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about our practices. Questions regarding this Privacy Statement could be directed to our [support team](mailto:service@ameya360.com).

#### Overview

Privacy is a concern to most Internet users. Ameya360 is acutely aware of, and sensitive to, the privacy concerns of our customers. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. If you are registering to use the site you will be asked to provide certain information. We are asking for this information solely for the purpose of providing the services offered and authenticating your identity when you login. Be assured that we do not sell information about our customers or site visitors to third parties.

#### Privacy Policy Enforcement

If you feel that Ameya360 is violating this Privacy Statement, please contact our [support team](mailto:service@ameya360.com).

#### Traffic Data

We collect click-stream data such as referring URL, browser and platform, time of visit, pages visited and searches performed. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our website and better serve our customers. We analyze this data to establish trends and help us improve your online experience. Aggregated traffic data may be shared with potential advertisers, research firms, and business partners for demographic purposes. When used in this aggregated form no one will be able to identify or contact you.

#### Use of E-mail Addresses

Any email sent by Ameya360 will contain unsubscribe information so that you may opt-out of future emails at any time. E-mails that confirm business transactions will always be sent to you.

#### Use of Cookies

A "cookie" is a piece of information that our website sends to your browser, which then stores this information on your system. A cookie allows our website to "remember" information about your preferences either until you exit your current browser window (if the cookie is temporary) or until you disable or delete the cookie. Many users prefer to use cookies to help them navigate a website as seamlessly as possible. You should be aware that cookies contain no more information than you volunteer, and they are not able to "invade" your hard drive and return to the sender with personal or other information from your computer. If you choose not to accept a cookie, you will not be able to use our website. 

#### Sending You Responses and Updates

We generally respond to any email questions, requests for service or information, and other inquiries we receive. We may also retain this correspondence to improve our products, services and website. Frequently we retain contact information so that we can send individuals updates or other important information about our services and products. 

#### Surveys

From time-to-time we may request information via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you always have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve this website, and to improve our customer service and product offerings. 

#### Security

Find out how we maintain a high level of security at our site. 

#### Terms of Use

The Ameya360 website may contain links to third-party sites. The linked sites are not under the control of Ameya360, and the Ameya360 is not responsible for the contents of any linked site, any link contained in a linked site, any changes or updates to such linked sites, or any transmission from any linked site. Ameya360 is providing these links to third-party sites only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Ameya360 of the site. 

#### License and Site Access

Ameya360 grants you a limited license to access and make personal use of this site and not to download (other than page caching) or modify it, or any portion of it, except with express written consent of Ameya360.

This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this site or its contents. Any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of this site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. 

This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without express written consent of Ameya360. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to the home page of www.ameya360.com so long as the link does not portray Ameya360, its parent company, or their products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive matter. You may not use any Ameya360 logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.
